<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>George Czabania</title>
    <link>https://george.czabania.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on George Czabania</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 17:42:02 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://george.czabania.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen: Sunday Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/kitchen-sunday-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 17:42:02 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/kitchen-sunday-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>This morning I made pancakes for breakfast. They turned out pretty well.
Recipe: http://thepioneerwoman.com/cooking/lemon-pancakes/
The video was originally published on my Snapchat story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen: Ginger Crunch</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/kitchen-ginger-crunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 17:34:31 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/kitchen-ginger-crunch/</guid>
      <description>This was a late night cooking experiment. Originally I wanted to make some bagels - but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough flour. A friend suggested I make this Ginger Crunch recipe instead - and it turned out pretty well.
Recipe: https://albrown.co.nz/cook/sweet-stuff/ginger-crunch
The video was originally published on my Snapchat story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixtape: A Midnight Bolt Of Electricity</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/mixtape-a-midnight-bolt-of-electricity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 17:39:55 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/mixtape-a-midnight-bolt-of-electricity/</guid>
      <description>Continuing to redub my mixtape collection, today I chose one of my favourite mixes - &amp;ldquo;A Midnight Bolt of Electricity&amp;rdquo; - for times when you just need some banging tunes.
This is the first cassette that I used the calibration feature to set the bias and recording level. I also checked the left/right balance by using a signal generator app to make sure that both channels were equal. The end result is that this is the best sounding cassette I have recorded to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixtape: Charles Bradley and Soul</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/mixtape-charles-bradley-and-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 22:12:29 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/mixtape-charles-bradley-and-soul/</guid>
      <description>Today I purchased my third cassette deck from Fred at retrotronics.co.nz. This one is a Sony TC-K615S and it&amp;rsquo;s an absolute beast of a machine. I chose it because it it is a 3-head cassette deck, that is in excellent condition and supports bias calibration. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably write a blog post about it sometime soon.
Anyway, the important thing is that the tapes I record with it sound a lot better than recordings I have made with my other decks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Film: Mt. Eden 2</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/instant-film-on-mt-eden-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 20:32:31 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/instant-film-on-mt-eden-2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a cold for the last couple of days and have been stuck inside with chicken noodle soup, lemon+honey drinks and a nose that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to stop sneezing - I considered trying for the world record of longest sneezing fit but the current world record is 977 days!
Instead I decided to venture outside for some fresh air, and ended up finding a hidden path to get up the side of Mt Eden and into Tahaki Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony TC-161SD Cassette Deck Repair</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/sony-tc-161-sd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 20:48:48 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/sony-tc-161-sd/</guid>
      <description>I quite like cassette tapes - particularly recording mixtapes.
I acquired a 1970&amp;rsquo;s Sony cassette deck earlier this year - I chose this one because of it&amp;rsquo;s gorgeous wooden plinth and top-loading cassette tray.
It plays back fine, and sounds pretty good for it&amp;rsquo;s age.
However, earlier today, the play button stopped working - I physically couldn&amp;rsquo;t depress the switch anymore. I removed the top and bottom covers to reveal the complex inner workings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Film: Mt. Eden</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/instant-film-on-mt-eden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 14:07:47 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/instant-film-on-mt-eden/</guid>
      <description>One of my goals for 2017 is to take an instant film photograph every single day.
Yesterday I had lunch at one of my favourite places in Mt Eden - on the actual mountain bit, not the suburb. As I was leaving I captured this photo of myself walking up a hill.
I hung the camera in a nearby tree and set the timer before rushing back to get in position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixtape: Life Below The Storm</title>
      <link>https://george.czabania.com/posts/life-below-the-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 09:08:19 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://george.czabania.com/posts/life-below-the-storm/</guid>
      <description>I woke up a cold this morning - and went out for a walk listening to my &amp;lsquo;Sick Days&amp;rsquo; mixtape I made the last time I had a cold. I decided to make a new mixtape for when I was feeling under the weather. It&amp;rsquo;s mainly based around some artists I have been listening to a lot lately.
Spotify Playlist:
 Cassette List:
Side A
 Earl St. Clair - Good Time Yukno - Sonne Portugal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>